eventtravel.com 2019-09-28

# Event Travel Privacy and Data Protection Policy

**PRIVACY AND DATA PROTECTION**

Event Travel only collects personal information about you (for example your name, address, telephone number, email address) but never credit/debit/payment card details during any on-line transaction and only when you specifically provide us with such information, on a voluntary basis, for example when purchasing or enquiring about event tickets, packages online. Any personal information Event Travel collect via our website will never be released or sold to any companies or individuals.

We will not share your personal information for marketing or any other purposes without your consent, unless where required by law. If you have registered your interest to subscribe to Event Travel's Newsletter and thereby given your consent, you will receive Event News and New Releases periodically but normally no more than one per week or only when a specific New Event is Announced to ensure you don't miss out on any Pre-Sale or On-Sale dates and times! _(You can of course unsubscribe at any time)_ As Event Travel act as __ Officially Appointed Agents for Artist(s)/Artist Management/Promoter/Global TourIng/Event Organisers, in some instances your email address may be required by the Artist/Promoter/Tour/Event Organiser, to ensure you receive the best and up to date event information in respect to the forthcoming show or other artist related information. _(You can of course unsubscribe at any time)_ In some cases your Name and Address information is required by the Promoter/Event Organiser for Security and Ticket Entry validation purposes and purely on a show by show basis only. Full compliance of Data Protection is in place at all times.

**Data Protection and Privacy**

Event Travel takes the security of your personal data extremely seriously and abides by the updated General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) effective from 25th May 2018 and which supersedes the previous Data Protection Act 1998. Please see below how we handle your personal data and what rights you have.

**What personal data is collected**

Personal data that you provide is likely to include but is not limited to:-

**• Name(s) including those as detailed in your booking  
• Gender  
• Age/DOB (where applicable)  
• Postal Address  
• Email Address  
• Phone Number(s)  
• IP Address (if booking on-line) **_this does not identify you personally_

You may also provide us with requests regarding special diet or special information in order to note in your booking on health grounds with a view to us assisting wherever possible in this regard.

Any personal data provided by you or others in your booking is solely used in connection with your booking with us and this information is given freely by you or on behalf of others in your booking, by telephone or when booking on-line via our website, email or fax. You may also choose to subscribe to our newsletter, which you can always unsubscribe from at any time, by selecting unsubscribe. You may also receive news alerts if you have subscribed to our social media options, including for example Facebook, Twitter, Instagram, LinkedIn, Google+, Pinterest, Our Blog.

**Purpose of personal data processing**

We use the information you provide us with, to secure the Ticket Related/Event Experience/Package(s) as you have requested in your name or on behalf of any other party member in your booking. By making a purchase from this site you are consenting to your financial and/or personal information being passed to any third party organisations necessary to process your transactions with Event Travel, such as credit/payment card companies, banks and the companies that handle transaction processing on our behalf. Except for these specific cases, we will never share financial information with third parties without your specific consent and again this would not relate to any payment card details which are not held/stored on our systems or by our company.

**Storage of personal data**

We store your personal information securely and may be held on our systems for up to 15 years, however, you can request that we delete your records at any time. If you have subscribed to our newsletter, we save your contact details until further notice. You can at any time, unsubscribe by selecting "unsubscribe" at the bottom of the newsletter or by emailing unsubscribe or by writing to us at the address below. Your contact details will be then deleted.

In some cases, we may need to store data for longer periods when required by law (e.g. accounting law) or, for example, complaints.

**Who may be processing personal data**

Your personal information is processed by our trained staff, our website system services and related administrative services, including PCI Compliant payment processing companies on our behalf with whom we have contract agreements for the protection of personal data .

Elements of your personal data may also be processed within the industry, such as venues, hotels/accommodation providers and transportation companies. This will only be as required, to fulfil our obligations to you, relating to the relevant elements of the services you require, in conjunction with the Ticket/Event Experience you have booked with us. As Event Travel act as appointed agents on an Official Basis, for Artist(s), Artist or Event Management and their Promoters, we may be required to share your data in respect to Ticket Validation and they may subsequently contact you to provide additional information concerning the Event or Show or to provide information relating to the security of the Event or Show and Artist/Event News - You can unsubscribe at any time from any information they provide.

**Processing of personal data in countries outside the EU and EEA**

Depending on the country/destination your Ticket/Event or Package you have booked is located and which partners we may use to fulfil our obligations to you, elements of your personal data may be processed outside the EU and EEA. Similarly if the destination of a Ticket/Event Experience or Package is within the EU/EEA, it may be the transport companies and accommodation organisations or partners we use, may be based outside the EU / EEA. This said, at all times only the necessary information required for the execution of the Ticket/Event Experience or Package and other services is provided to our contracted partners.

By submitting your personal information to us, you agree that we may process personal data outside the EU and the EEA and that you are aware that privacy data protection may be lower than that legislated in the EU and EEA.

**Your rights to information about you.**

You have the right, at any time, to withdraw your consent to processing the information you have provided to us.

This means that you can also request rectification or deletion of your personal information. Such a request is to be made in writing to us. Your data will then be corrected or deleted as soon as possible and within a month of your request. If you have a current Ticket/Event Experience or Package booking that has yet to take place or has completed, your data on your request will be deleted as soon as is possible to do or within one month after completion of the Ticket/Event Experience or Package unless otherwise required by law.

You can access your booking at any time using CUSTOMER LOGIN with your password and email to view your personal information we store about you and your booking(s) with us. You can also correct and update this information. You can also contact us with the request to have access to the registered information we have about you, which we will provide as soon as is possible and within a month of any request.

**Cookie Declaration**  
eventtravel.com uses cookies.

**What are cookies?**  
Cookies are small text files that are placed on your computer, smartphone or other device when you access the internet.

**Why are cookies essential to eventtravel.com website?**  
This website, along with most websites, uses cookies. Cookies let users navigate around the site. Without cookies enabled we can't guarantee that the website and your experience would be as we would wish. IMPORTANT TO KNOW:- None of the cookies we use collect your personal information and they cannot be used to identify you. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the statistical data you choose to share with us.

**Want to know more about the Data Protection Ordinance (GDPR)?**

More information on the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) is available on the data inspection [website](https://ico.org.uk/your-data-matters/).

If you would like to contact us, please do so at Event Travel, 90 Calverley Road, Tunbridge Wells, Kent. TN1 2UN - United Kingdom, please email [Customer Support](mailto:customersupport@eventtravel.com?subject=GDPR)

**Security Measures - PCI Compliant**

We take the security of your personal information very seriously. Consequently we use 128 bit Secure Socket Layer (SSL) encryption for all your transactions with  Event Travel . This system encrypts all your personal information and all Debit/Credit Card/PayPal payments are transacted by [**BRAINTREE**](https://www.braintreepayments.com/en-gb/about-braintree) a **PayPal company** which is fully PCI compliant so that no card data is stored or can be read or intercepted by a malicious third party.

**Third Party Sites**

Event Travel  is not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of any third party sites linked to this site. Consequently we advise you to read their privacy policies before submitting data to such sites.

**Customer Support**

If we can assist further please email [Customer Support](mailto:customersupport@eventtravel.com?subject=Privacy) \- thank you.
